本字幕由诸神字幕组出品，仅供学习交流，禁止用于商业用途
更多中日双语字幕，尽在 www.kamigami.org 和微博 @诸神字幕组
This nonstop rain is depressing...
こう雨が続くと　気が滅入るな
Morning, Ohta.
おはよう　太田
Oh, morning, Tanaka.
おはよう　田中
Man, the rain makes it so humid. It's killing me.
いやあ　雨が降ると湿度が高くなってほんとまいるね
I don't think humidity's the problem here.
湿度がどうかという以前に　完全なるびちゃびちゃだぞ　それは
You're absolutely drenched.
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
After school I sit next to a window
眠たい放課後　窓から見下ろす
And the spring breeze entices me to sleep
春風なびいて　ひと休み
So I shut an eye against the dazzling world
日听
gen & AB
翻译
颜歌＆沐沐
眩しい世界に　片目を瞑れば
日校
小伍
校对
戚风
While the sun makes the scenery dance upon my eyelids
时轴
WEI&和路雪
压制
wedy96
映し出す景色躍りだす
负责人
戚风
I whistle vaguely at the blue sky
頼りない口笛　青空に吹けば
足取りもちょっと軽くなる
And I get more of a spring in my step
I remove my earphones in a bustling corner of the city
騒がしい街角　イヤフォン外して
And look into the distance, where I hear a voice
見上げたら遠く声がする
Let's bask in the glowing sun
さぁ陽の光浴びてゆるやかに
Ever so gently
いつもの今日が始まる
Starting another day as usual
サンシャインと居眠りする
Napping in the sunshine
心地いい場所　君の隣で
In this cozy place with you
With all these feelings booming in my heart
優しく胸に響いてる
字幕
诸神字幕组
Episode 6
The Sick Tanaka-kun
My sister told me to take an umbrella
because there was an 80% chance of rain.
降水確率８０％だから傘いるよって妹に言われて
So I left home with one...
持って出たんだけど
It won't be necessary for this amount of rain.
これくらいなら　ワザワザささなくていっか
It wasn't raining very hard when I left the house.
家出た時はほとんど降ってなかったんだよね
But with every passing moment...
けど　そのあと…
I'll make it.
まだいける
And before I knew it, it was raining cats and dogs.
気づいたら　結構な豪雨だったっぽい
Your umbrella must've felt miserable,
すぐ側にいながら　役目を果たせなかった傘の気持ちを考えると
being so close, yet unable to fulfill its duty.
切ないな
I don't really like umbrellas to begin with.
そもそもそんなに傘が好きじゃないんだよね
My hands get wet every time I open or close them.
さしたり畳んだりする度に手が濡れるし
There's no place to put them on buses and trains.
バスや電車の中で置き場所に困るし
Also, I tend to forget them somewhere,
あと気づいたら　どこかに忘れてきちゃって　何本も買うハメになるし
and I have to buy a new one every time.
Well, I guess they can be a pain,
まあ　不便なところもあるかもしれんが
but I think they're generally useful tools.
基本的には役に立つ道具だと思うぞ
If you think back, I'm sure there have been
several occasions where they've helped you.
思い返してみれば田中だって　今まで助けられた場面が多々あったはずだ
Helped me...
助けられたこと…
Oh, yeah...
そうだ
One day, when I had nothing to lean against,
何ももたれかかる物がない場所で
あの日のあいつは杖として俺をしっかり支えてくれた
the umbrella supported me firmly as a cane.
I could hear the umbrella's
pride shattering just now.
傘のプライド　バキバキに折れる音がしたぞ　今
It sure is pouring.
雨　よく降るな
I know it's cliché,
ベタかもしれないけど
but how nice would it be to share
an umbrella with the person you love?
雨の日に好きな人と相合傘って憧れちゃうな
Oh, gosh... I'm thinking about it so much,
it's starting to look like he's actually there.
やだ　考えすぎてまるでそこにいるような気がしてきちゃった
A soaking wet Tanaka-kun...
ずぶ濡れの田中くんが…
That's actually him!
って　本物だー
T-Tanaka-kun, what are you doing?!
た…田中くん　何してるの
Tanaka!
田中　急にいなくなったと思ったら
You disappeared on me!
What are you doing out here?
こんなところで何を
The bodies of insects and birds
虫とか鳥とかの体って　身を守るために便利に進化したりするじゃん
conveniently evolve to keep them safe, right?
So I thought, if I kept standing out
in the rain like that, I might...
だから　ああやって雨に打たれ続けることで
Tanaka has acquired the
special ability "Rain Barrier"!
...be able to achieve a very
convenient constitution, too.
っていうものすごく便利な体に俺もなれたりするんじゃないかなーと思って
If mankind had that kind of latent potential,
人類がそんな潜在能力を秘めてたら
it would've been unlocked
long ago by our ancestors,
傘のない時代を生き延びてきたご先祖たちが
who survived the age before umbrellas.
とっくの昔に開花させてたと思うぞ
In any case, your hatred for umbrellas
runs a lot deeper than I thought.
それにしても　お前の傘嫌いは思った以上に筋金入りだな
Well, they're such a pain.
だって　めんどくさいんだもん
I see now.
なるほど　傘さすのが面倒で雨バリアーとか言ってたんだ
He was talking about a "rain barrier"
because he doesn't want to use an umbrella.
Using an umbrella might be bothersome,
傘をさすの　面倒かもしれないけど
体が濡れて風邪でも引いたらしんどくて
but if you catch a cold from
being wet, you'll feel worse,
and that could be even more bothersome.
もっと面倒なことになるんじゃないかな
That's a good point.
言われてみれば確かに
Okay, I'll use my umbrella properly.
じゃあ　やっぱりちゃんと傘使う
You're serious, Tanaka?
本当か　田中
Nice job, Shiraishi!
さすがだぞ　白石
Y-Yeah... I'm glad.
よかった
I just remembered another thing
I hate about umbrellas...
傘の嫌いなところ　もう一つあった
People always grab mine
and take it home by mistake.
すぐ間違えて誰かに持って帰られるところ
I go in a different direction from here,
so could you take over, Shiraishi?
ここから先　俺は別方向だから
あとは白石頼むな
B-But... I...
で…でも　あの…
God, Buddha, Ohta-sama...
神様　仏様　太田様
Shiraishi-san, can I scoot closer to you?
白石さん　もうちょっとそっち寄ってもいい？
No...
いや　これ以上は心臓が心配だから　無理かも
I'm afraid any closer might be bad
for my heart, so that's no good!
Okay...
そっか
This is awful...
最悪だ
I panicked and rejected him flat-out.
焦りすぎて思いっきり拒否しちゃったよ
But...
けど…
Being this close is more than enough for me.
私にとっては　十分すぎるくらい近い距離だな
My shoulder's freezing...
肩　冷たい
I want to move further under the umbrella...
もっと内側に入りたい
Morning.
おはよう
This again?
またか
You realized too late that it was a downpour?
今日も気づいたら豪雨だったのか
What happened to your resolve from yesterday?
昨日の決意はどうした
No...
いや
With today's rain, I thought if I just
dodged between the raindrops,
今日くらいの雨なら　雨と雨の合間をくぐり抜ければ
I could make it here without getting wet.
濡れずにたどり着けるんじゃないかと思って
But it was beyond my capabilities.
けど　今の俺には高度すぎた
伊賀か甲賀で修業を積めば　あるいは…
I must train in either Iga or Koga, or perhaps...
It's about 500 times easier to just use an umbrella.
もうそれ　傘さす方が５００倍くらい楽だぞ
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
Tanaka-kun Is Always Listless
Whoa, that's awful, Tanaka.
ひどいな　田中
I barely recognized you.
別人みたいだな
Master...
師匠が…
Morning. What's up?
おはよう
どうしたんだ
Morning, Ohta...
おはよう　太田
You sound terrible. Are you sick?
ひどい声だな　風邪か
Seems like it...
そうみたい
Master! Master!
U-Um, are you okay, Tanaka-kun?
Is it because you were out in the rain?
師匠が師匠が…
あの　田中くん　大丈夫？
もしかして雨に打たれたせいで
師匠が師匠が…
Master! Master!
My throat hurts a little, that's all.
ちょっと喉が痛いだけだから
You gave me good advice,
and I still got sick. I'm sorry.
せっかく白石さんにアドバイスもらったのに　ごめんね
Don't worry about that.
ううん　無理しないで
I'll take you to the nurse's office
if you're not feeling well.
辛くなったらいつでも保健室行こう
Thanks, but I'm fine.
ありがとう　大丈夫だから
I don't want you to catch it,
so you'd best stay away.
それに移るといけないから　離れて
If you start feeling really bad,
I'll take you to the nurse's office.
まあ　無理そうだったら　俺が保健室に連れていこう
Everyone spaces out when they're sick.
風邪を引くと頭がぼーっとするからな
Tanaka is sluggish to begin with,
so he'll probably move even slower.
ただでさえ鈍い田中の動きがさらに鈍くなりそうだ
I'd better keep an eye on him...
気をつけてやらんと
A-Are you okay, Tanaka?!
だ…大丈夫か　田中
His movements are actually more violent than usual.
むしろ平常時より動きは激しいな
I feel as though my strength is
なんか俺の意思に反して　体力がどんどん消耗していく
gradually depleting against my will...
You can't do anything about
those coughs that crawl up on you.
込み上げてくる咳はどうしようもないからな
Judging by your voice,
it's really taking a toll on your throat.
あと声を聞く限り　かなり喉に来てるな
You should try to avoid talking
so it doesn't get worse.
悪化しないよう　今日は極力喋らないようにしろ
But if you can't speak,
I wonder how we should communicate...
しかし　喋らないとなるとどうコミュニケーションを取るべきか悩むな
That won't be a problem...
それなら大丈夫
Huh?
What?
なんだ
Between you and me,
lip reading should suffice.
俺と太田の仲なら　口パクで十分
Tanaka, do you know which part
of your body that mask is covering?
田中　今お前のマスクがどこを隠してるかわかるか
Lip reading is difficult, so let's
communicate through writing.
Okay.
Such tiny handwriting...
Wait, is this kanji right?
あれ　この漢字これで合ってるか
Sorry, could you hang on a sec, Tanaka?
すまん　ちょっと待ってくれ　田中
I'll look it up real quick. Let's see...
すぐ調べる
えーっと
You can just talk
normally, you know.
Oh, no, Ohta. I forgot
my Japanese History textbook.
Seriously?
マジか
Why don't you ask Echizen in the class
next door if you can borrow hers?
隣のクラスの越前に貸してもらったらどうだ
Oh, no, Ohta. I forgot
my Japanese History textbook.
Someone else,
if possible...
But we don't know anyone in
the other classes except Echizen...
けど　越前くらいしか他のクラスの知り合いいないしな
... True.
Oh, hey, Tanaka. What's up?
田中じゃねぇか　なんか用か
The name "Echizen" takes so much
time to write. What a pain.
越前って苗字　書くのに時間かかってめんどい
What are you doing?
なんだよ
You should change
your surname to
"Ohta" or "Tanaka"
A proposal from you?
Not in 1oo years!
-Echizen
A proposal from you?
Not in 1oo years!
-Echizen
How did a conversation about
a Japanese History textbook lead to that?
どうやったら日本史の教科書からそういう話になるんだ
A proposal from you?
Not in 1oo years!
-Echizen
A proposal from you?
Not in 1oo years!
-Echizen
A proposal from you?
Not in 1oo years!
-Echizen
No idea...
A proposal from you?
If communicating through writing
is too hard, we could try gesturing.
筆談が難しいならジェスチャーにしてみるか
In this case, my comprehension skill
will be vital to understanding you...
この場合伝わるかどうかは俺の理解力が重要になってくるな
Try something so we can practice, Tanaka.
練習がてら何かやってみてくれ　田中
Tired.
だるい
Sleepy.
眠い
結構いけるね　さすが太田
It's working pretty well. Nice, Ohta.
Yeah, this is going great.
ああ　これはなかなかいいぞ　思ったよりわかる
It's easier than I expected.
Won't you need a method to convey
other messages besides those two?
その２つ以外を伝える手段が必要なんじゃ…
Is he trying to awaken a new ability
again because he's too lazy to talk?!
まさか喋るのがだるすぎて
また新しい能力に目覚めようとしているのか
Tanaka has acquired the
psychic ability "Telepathy"!
It's easier to just talk, so I'll talk...
もう普通に喋った方が楽だし　喋る
I-I see... So you gave up on telepathy.
そ　そうか
テレパシーは諦めたんだな
Huh?
田中　なんかいつもより肌がツヤっとしてないか
Tanaka... Is it just me or is your
skin more radiant than usual?
I've been wearing a mask, so my breath
must have moisturized my skin...
マスクしてたから　自分の息で潤ったのかも
I see. That's an unexpected effect.
なるほど　意外な効果だ
Also, I actually figured out a new game
I can play while wearing a mask.
あと実は　この状態でできる新しい遊びも思いついたんだよね
It's quite fun.
なかなか楽しい
Oh?
I guess you discover new things
when in unusual circumstances.
いつもと違う状態だと　いろいろ新発見があるな
I'm glad you were able to get
something out of being sick.
しんどいなりに　得られるものがあってよかった
Morning, Tanaka.
おはよう　田中
Oh, good.
おお　よかった
マスクが取れたということは風邪治ったんだな
You're not wearing a mask,
so I assume you're feeling better?
Yeah. Morning, Ohta.
うん　おはよう　太田
What's wrong, Tanaka?
どうした　田中
Your usual listlessness is gone.
いつものけだるさがまったくないぞ
Are you coming down with
something other than a cold now?
風邪じゃなくて今度は何か別の病気なんじゃ…
Oh, yeah... I'm not wearing a mask...
そっか　マスクない
Whoops...
しまった
Lately, I've been making weird faces
under the mask where no one could see,
見えないのをいいことに
ここ最近ずっとマスクの下で変顔してたから
so my facial muscles have become more active.
表情筋が無駄に活発に
My cold might be gone,
but I'm going to wear the mask today, too.
風邪治ったけど　やっぱり今日もマスクしとく
Well, um... It's nice to see
that side of you now and then...
いや　まぁ　たまにはそういうお前もいいんじゃないか
It might take a few more days
for him to completely return to normal.
本来の田中を取り戻すまで　更にあと数日かかりそうだな
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
The power of a common cold is frightening...
恐るべし　風邪の威力
What should I do? I had no idea!
どうしよう　全然気づかなかった
You should change
your surname to
"Ohta" or "Tanaka"
Is it going to be me or Ohta? It's your choice.
俺か太田か　どっちか選びなよ
ま…まさか　あいつらが求婚するほどあたしのことを好きだなんて
To think... Those two love me so much,
they actually want to marry me!
Tanaka didn't seem like
he was interested in me at all.
だって田中とか　まったくあたしに興味なさそうだったじゃん
If anything, he seemed to think I was an annoyance...
むしろウザがってそうに見えたのに
And Ohta is a childhood friend.
ましてや太田は幼馴染
It's too late for me to see him as a man.
今更そんな男として意識するなんて…
I just can't!
できないよ
Who's that?
誰？
That long skirt...
そのスカートの長さ　もしかして越前さん？
Is it you, Echizen-san? What are you doing?
何してるの
Tanaka
Kingdom
Constitutional
Promulgation
Tanaka
Kingdom
Constitutional
Promulgation
Sorry, but a "no fighting" decree
悪いけど　今週に入って
Tanaka
Kingdom
Constitutional
Promulgation
Tanaka
Kingdom
Constitutional
Promulgation
Tanaka
Kingdom
Constitutional
Promulgation
Tanaka
Kingdom
Constitutional
Promulgation
Tanaka
Kingdom
Constitutional
Promulgation
Tanaka
Kingdom
Constitutional
Promulgation
Tanaka
Kingdom
Constitutional
Promulgation
has been issued this week in the Tanaka Kingdom.
「喧嘩売買禁止令」が発令されたから　田中王国
No Fighting
Decree
Tanaka
Wha—No!
なっ　違う
I'm not gonna fight. I'm a girl.
喧嘩なんてそんな…
女の子だし
Oh, so you've changed your mind, Echizen?
考えは改めたのか　越前
I hope we don't have heavy snow tomorrow...
明日の天気　豪雪とか困る
Does that mean you like me just the way I am?
それってつまり　そのままの君が好きってこと？
That reminds me.
Echizen, I've been thinking...
そうだ　越前　考えてみたんだが
If you want to challenge Tanaka again,
how about a thumb wrestle?
もし次に田中と勝負するなら　指相撲はどうだ
It's peaceful, but determining the winner is simple.
平和だが　勝敗はわかりやすいぞ
Good idea. It's like the epitome
of an energy-saving match.
いいね　省エネルギーでできる勝負代表って感じがする
Right? It requires technique more than strength.
だろう
力というより　テクニックが重要だしな
B-But...
そっ　そんな
If Ohta or Tanaka were to grab my hand now...
今　太田や田中に手を握られたりなんかしたら…
I caught you.
捕まえた
あたし…あたし…
I'll... I'll...
I'll die from my heart bursting!
心臓が張り裂けて死んじゃう
Is thumb wrestling that
life-threatening in delinquent society?
ヤンキー界の指相撲　そんな命がけなのか
To think Ohta and Tanaka,
それにしても　太田と田中
two guys who are polar opposites,
would propose to me...
まったく正反対の二人からプロポーズされるとはな
Which type is the best fit for me?
あたしに合うのはどっちのタイプなんだろう
Kind
Reliable
Will probably
treat me like
a girl
Will probably
treat me like
a girl
Echizen, I...
越前　俺は…
Don't treat me like a girl!
女の子扱いするなー
Beats him up out of embarrassment
Listless
Unreliable
Not even sure
if he'll treat me
like a human
Not even sure
if he'll treat me
like a human
越前さん
Echizen-san...
Treat me more like a wife!
もっと嫁として扱え
Beats him up out of sheer anger
I have no choice but to change myself...
自分が変わるしかない
I can... I can do it...
なれる　なれるよ
I can be a normal girl...
普通の女の子に
E-E-Ecchan?! What are you doing?!
え…ええっ　えっちゃん　何してるの
You scared me.
びっくりした
You can't do that, Ecchan.
This skirt is important to you.
えっちゃんダメだよ　大事なスカートなのに
Myaano...
みゃーの…
That's right...
そうだ　苗字が変わったら　みゃーのからの呼ばれ方も変わっちまう
If my surname changes,
Myaano will have to call me by a different name...
M-Myaano...
み…みゃーの
If my surname changed to Tanaka
or Ohta, what would you call me?
もし　あたしの苗字が田中か太田になったら　なんて呼ぶ
Um... It's Ecchan because you're Echizen,
ええっと　越前でえっちゃんだから
so if you're Tanaka, you'll be Tacchan.
田中ならたっちゃんで　太田なら…
If you're Ohta, you'll be...
Occhan?
おっちゃん？
No...
ダメだ　みゃーのにおっさん扱いされるなんて
I can't handle Myaano calling me
the same thing people call old men!
辛すぎる
I guess it's Tanaka, then...
…田中かな
Speak of the devil! There's Master!
噂をすれば師匠発見です
Master! How are you feeling?!
I'm feeling very energetic!
師匠　調子はいかがですか
私はとっても元気です
Yeah, I can see that.
うん　見ればわかる
Also, I'm pretty much never energetic.
あと　俺は基本的に元気ないから
Myaano is small, so her height
difference with Tanaka works well.
みゃーのはちっさいから　田中と並ぶと身長差いい感じだな
I'm nearly the same height as Tanaka,
あたしなんか　田中とほぼ同じくらいだし
so I wouldn't look cute next to him...
隣に並んでも可愛げがないな
あたしもみゃーのくらい背低くて可愛らしかったらな
I wish I were short and cute like Myaano...
Why?! Ecchan, you look so cool and gorgeous!
なんで　えっちゃんかっこよくて素敵なのに
I admire people who are tall and strong, too.
俺も　背高くて力のある人いいと思う
Huh?!
R-R-Really?
そ…そそそうかよ
まぁべっ別に嬉しくな…な…なんか　ないけど
It's n-not like h-hearing that
makes me h-happy or a-anything...
Wh-Wh-What's wrong, Ecchan?
You're stuttering like crazy!
どどどどどうしたの　えっちゃん　噛みまくりだよ
In fact, I'd like her to aim for Ohta's level...
むしろ　太田レベルを目指して頑張ってほしい
I see.
そっか　背の高さとかあんまり気にしなくていいんだな
I guess I don't need to be concerned about height.
Watch out!
危ない
Are you okay, Echizen?
大丈夫か　越前
What is this sense of safety?
なに　この包容力
I fit perfectly in his arms...
すっぽりおさまってるんですけど
His hands are so big...
Wait, isn't his face kinda close?
手とかでかくて　っていうか　顔近くないですか
This body temperature or whatever
it is I'm feeling can't be good...
ちょっとその体温めいたものがやばいんですけど
Echizen!
越前
Why'd you run off without any warning?
どうしたんだ　いきなり
Here, grab my hand.
ほら　掴まれ
Don't... This is nothing—
バ…　これくらい大丈…
Ow...
って
Don't try to move so much.
無理に動くな
What if you have a sprained ankle?
捻挫でもしていたらどうする
P-Put me down! Put me down right now!
お…おろせ　今すぐおろせ
Hey, Echizen! Stop flailing!
こら　越前　暴れるな
Are you okay?
大丈夫か
Seriously, what's gotten into you, Echizen?
ほんとにどうした　越前
You're acting strange today.
今日は様子がおかしいぞ
Did you eat something weird?
何か変なものでも食べた？
I-It's because...
だ…だって
Y-You guys asked me to
お…お前らがあたしに…
use either Ohta's or Tanaka's name!
太田か田中のどっちか名乗れとか言うから
Hold on, Echizen. What are you talking about?
ちょっと待て　越前　何のことだ
Huh?! You're gonna play dumb
after asking me something that important?!
あんな大事なこと言っといて今更惚ける気？
Sorry, I seriously don't know. Please enlighten me.
いや　すまん　真面目にわからんから教えてくれ
You bastard! You're making a girl say it?!
てめぇな　女に言わせてんじゃねぇよ
A man should be more assertive!
男ならもっとグイグイ来い
If you do, I'll obey and follow you...
そしたらあたしだって３歩下がってだな
She's surprisingly old-fashioned...
意外と古風
Ohta or Tanaka...
太田か田中…
越前さん　もしかして俺が風邪引いてた時のこれ？
Echizen-san, are you talking about
what I wrote when I was sick?
You should change
your surname to
"Ohta" or "Tanaka"
You should change
your surname to
"Ohta" or "Tanaka"
You should change
your surname to
"Ohta" or "Tanaka"
Y-Yeah, that!
You just popped that out of nowhere!
そ…そうだよ　それだよ
い…いきなりあんなことを
I see... You've been concerned over
something like that all this time?
そっか　ずっとそんなこと気にしてたんだ
Oh, I shouldn't call it "something like that." Sorry.
いや　そんなこととか言っちゃ失礼だね　ごめん
A-As long as we understand each other, it's fine...
わ…わかってるならいいんだよ　べっ別に
画数が多くて書くのがだるいなんて理由で
I'm truly sorry I disrespected your precious surname
just because it has so many strokes
that I was too lazy to write it.
越前さんの大切な苗字を侮辱したりして　ほんとごめん
Huh?
So that's what happened.
そんなことがあったのか
Yeah.
So I thought it'd be easier if you changed your name
だから
簡単に書ける太田とか田中にいっそ苗字を変えてくれたら楽なのに
to something easier to write, like Ohta or Tanaka.
って思っちゃったんだけど
I had no idea you were
that fond of your own surname.
まさか越前さん　自分の苗字にそこまで愛着があったとは
I apologize.
申し訳ない
So...
えっと　つまり書くのがめんどくさかったっていうだけで
Is he telling me he was just too lazy to write it?
Don't worry.
大丈夫　体調よければそこまで書くのだるくないから　越前
"Echizen" isn't so bothersome
to write when I'm not sick.
Yeah, Echizen. Tanaka was sick that day.
そうだ　越前　田中はあの日風邪だったんだ
Please forgive him.
許してやってくれ
It wasn't a marriage proposal at all...
全然求婚とかじゃなくて　全部あたしの勘違い
I just had the wrong idea about everything?!
Echizen is a good surname.
越前　いい苗字だよ
紛らわしいことしてんじゃねー
Don't say such damn misleading things!
Oh, there's a simpler way
別に苗字変えなくても
of referring to her without
having her change her name.
越前さんのままでもっと簡単に呼べる方法あった
Yeah.
Ecchan.
えっちゃん
Wha—
I see. "Ecchan."
なるほど　えっちゃん
It's easier to say out loud, too. "Ecchan."
声に出すのも楽だね　えっちゃん
S-Stop that! Don't repeat it!
ちょ…やめろ　連呼してんじゃねぇよ
Ecchan, my mom said to come visit us sometime.
えっちゃん　たまにはうちに来てって母が言ってたぞ
Ecchan. It has a nice ring to it. Ecchan.
えっちゃん　いいと思う
えっちゃん
Ecchan.
Everyday life is like a bothersome cat
BON-BON　いつもの　いたずら猫みたい
How I wish I could ignore it and do as I please
自然体で　ワガママしたい
I discreetly retreat into my own world of music
気ままミュージック　こっそりノリノリで
Maybe I have a talent for daydreaming
空想なら得意かも
いわゆる幸せ　それってなぁに？
That so-called happiness
What exactly is it?
I tried acting on my own desires
好きなこと　とことん　やってみて
わかるのかなぁ
Will I understand it now?
Dramatic listlessness
BON-BON　ドラマチック
I want to put my life into its hands
「そこそこ」が希望
Maybe a positive attitude is better
ポジティブチケット　持ってたいね
Is trying my best the right thing to do?
精一杯なら　正解なのかな
I can't hold a poker face
ポーカーフェイスは苦手です
Everyday life makes me dizzy
グルグルしちゃうね
BON-BON　KUBBIDYU
My dear listlessness
Once more
もう一回
My dear listlessness
BON-BON　KUBBIDYU
It's Valentine's Day!
バレンタインです
Was it you?
お前か
Huh?
Are you the culprit?
お前が犯人か
It's Lady Macarons!
マカロンさんだ
Thank you for always
taking care of my brother.
兄がいつもお世話になってます
Next time, Episode 7:
Next Episode
Tanaka
次回　第７話「田中くんのバレンタイン」
Tanaka-kun's Valentine.